<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!-- This is a WordPress eXtended RSS file generated by WordPress as an export of your site. -->
<!-- It contains information about your site's posts, pages, comments, categories, and other content. -->
<!-- You may use this file to transfer that content from one site to another. -->
<!-- This file is not intended to serve as a complete backup of your site. -->

<!-- To import this information into a WordPress site follow these steps: -->
<!-- 1. Log in to that site as an administrator. -->
<!-- 2. Go to Tools: Import in the WordPress admin panel. -->
<!-- 3. Install the "WordPress" importer from the list. -->
<!-- 4. Activate & Run Importer. -->
<!-- 5. Upload this file using the form provided on that page. -->
<!-- 6. You will first be asked to map the authors in this export file to users -->
<!--    on the site. For each author, you may choose to map to an -->
<!--    existing user on the site or to create a new user. -->
<!-- 7. WordPress will then import each of the posts, pages, comments, categories, etc. -->
<!--    contained in this file into your site. -->

<!-- generator="WordPress/4.2.2" created="2015-06-19 22:53" -->
<rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:excerpt="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/excerpt/"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:wp="http://wordpress.org/export/1.2/"
>

<channel>
	<title>shyCYBORG STUDIOS</title>
	<link>http://www.shycyborg.com</link>
	<description>Turning Ideas into Fast, Effective Websites</description>
	<pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 22:53:30 +0000</pubDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<wp:wxr_version>1.2</wp:wxr_version>
	<wp:base_site_url>http://www.shycyborg.com</wp:base_site_url>
	<wp:base_blog_url>http://www.shycyborg.com</wp:base_blog_url>

	<wp:author><wp:author_id>1</wp:author_id><wp:author_login>david@shycyborg.com</wp:author_login><wp:author_email>david@shycyborg.com</wp:author_email><wp:author_display_name><![CDATA[David Green]]></wp:author_display_name><wp:author_first_name><![CDATA[David]]></wp:author_first_name><wp:author_last_name><![CDATA[Green]]></wp:author_last_name></wp:author>


	<generator>http://wordpress.org/?v=4.2.2</generator>

	<item>
		<title>Gain Confidence by Giving Compliments</title>
		<link>http://www.shycyborg.com/gain-confidence-giving-compliments/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 13:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[david@shycyborg.com]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://109.73.239.233/~shycybor/?p=344</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It’s obvious that receiving compliments can boost your self-confidence, but I’ve found giving compliments boosts my confidence as well.</p>

<p>Several times I’ve had an idea that I wasn’t sure about until I shared it with my wife and she complimented it. Knowing she had really thought about my idea, considered it, and still complimented it gave me the confidence to try it.</p>

<p>But I wouldn’t be so confident if she had simply said, “Oh yeah, that’s a great idea.” I would start having all sorts of doubts because I got a generic, dishonest compliment.</p>

<p>If the best compliments I receive are those where the other person really looked at me to see my positive attributes before making a compliment then I should do the same to others. After all, typically you get out of other people what you put into them.</p>

<p>It takes some work, but once you develop the habit of looking closely at other people in order to make an honest compliment you’ll eventually find yourself noticing your own positive attributes. When you do, go ahead and give yourself the compliment.</p>

<blockquote><p><b>Sanity Note:</b> Give yourself the compliment in your head, or at least not while around other people. Keep talking to yourself out loud and it might become hard to find people who stay around you long enough to give or take compliments.</p></blockquote>

<p>When you always look for darkness you find it and it overshadows your life, but when you make yourself look on the bright side of things you start noticing just how much light there really is in and around you.</p>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>344</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-09-26 13:06:57</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-09-26 13:06:57</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>gain-confidence-giving-compliments</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_yoast_wpseo_focuskw</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[confidence]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_yoast_wpseo_linkdex</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[76]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_encloseme</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_encloseme</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Consistent Style</title>
		<link>http://www.shycyborg.com/consistent-style/</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2014 02:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[david@shycyborg.com]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://109.73.239.233/~shycybor/?p=350</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[[caption id="attachment_351" align="alignright" width="250"]<img src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/inconsistent-fashion.jpg" alt="These inconsistent outfits only work because the girls are cute." width="250" height="331" class="size-full wp-image-351 topimage" /> These inconsistent outfits only work because the girls are cute.[/caption]

<p>Most of us tend to wear certain styles of clothing more than others. You might wear dark clothing, or never wear shorts, or always accessorize with a purse (I do not.) Other people become used to this style, and it can get some interesting reactions when we change things up - second glances, compliments from unexpected sources, quiet questioning of whether you’re color blind…</p>

<p>That’s great, usually, but we don’t want interesting reactions on a website. We want predictable. We want to visitors to reliably take the most important action, whether that be leave a comment, sign up for our mailing list, or buy a product.
</p>

<p>The most successful businesses don’t look at potential customers and think, "Well I wonder what they’ll do today." They observe the actions past customers take, or perhaps in the case of a new business, the actions customers at other businesses take. Then they try to figure out what caused the customers to take those actions so they can repeat them. This is called analytics, and I plan to cover that in a future post.</p>

<p>Another key component to guiding users to take the action you want is consistent style. Companies will spend thousands and thousands of dollars on analytics and A/B testing their sites, but still miss the easy wins like this one. I don't want you to miss it. If you ever bring a design to me to turn into a website I’ll point out this issue in your design. For now though, I’m going to give you a few examples of what to do and what to avoid.</p>

<h2>Consistent with Other Websites</h2>

<p>It’s your website, so you should be able to do things however you want to, right? If only. Well, you can, but it can sabotage your site and business.</p>

<p><span class="bigbluetext">Imagine:</span> You visit a website for a company you love. We'll call them <b>Cute Kittens R Us</b>.</p>
[caption id="attachment_369" align="aligncenter" width="500"]<img src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/cute-kittens.jpg" alt="Photo credit goes to Mathias Erhart" width="500" height="264" class="size-full wp-image-369" /> Photo credit goes to <a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/mathias-erhart/2562106102/" target="_blank">Mathias Erhart</a>[/caption]

<p>Once you stop awww'ing over the big picture of a kitten working a cash register on their home page you decide you want to look at the other pages of their website. So you look at the top of the page. Do you see a menu? Nope; just an advertisement for kitty litter.</p>

<p>You look at the left side of the website for the menu. See it? No, but you spend 5 seconds looking at that picture of the cat working the register again.</p>

<p>Finally you look at the right side of the website and hurriedly the bottom. You can’t find the menu because the designer wanted to be original and make the menu appear only after you click the cat’s paw as though you’re giving him money. Neat idea, but nobody except the designer ever finds the menu.</p>

<p>Is this an extreme example? Yes, but I needed an excuse to talk about cute kittens in order to make you like me more. Do I see real sites that hide their navigation in obscure places to fit in with their design? Absolutely.</p>

<p>I’ve been guilty of this myself in the past, but I realized no level of originality and awesomeness is worth confusing the visitors to my website. I want people to use my website, not curse it.</p>

<p>Your website doesn’t have to look like every other website, but people have come to expect certain things about websites and it wouldn’t hurt to abide by them, or at least not hide them under the picture of a cat. Here are a few things to keep in mind:</p>

<ul>
<li>Logos tend to go at the top-left of a website or the top-center. <b>And you should be able to click the logo to go back to the home page.</b></li>
<li>Your menu should be at the top or side of your site somewhere easy to find. If you have to click a button to see the menu you better make it easy to distinguish from the rest of the design.</li>
<li>Links should be visibly different than the other content on your page. Don’t have a black link within a paragraph of black text. Make it a different color (and not just when your mouse moves over it.) Or underline it. Or put a cat pointing to it with the caption, "Click. Link. Meow."</li>
<li>People expect Home, About, and Contact pages. When you give your pages clever names it confuses even me, and I’m supposed to be young and tech savvy.</li>
</ul>


<h2>Consistent Style Within Your Website</h2>

<p>Now, an example for the dog people.</p><p><span class="bigbluetext">Imagine:</span>  You go to look at the imaginary web page of <b>Pup Pop Mart</b>, where they sell sodas for dogs, because corporations think dog owners will buy anything for their dog (and they do).</p>

[caption id="attachment_371" align="aligncenter" width="400"]<img src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/puppy.jpg" alt="Photo credit goes to Viktor Hanacek" width="400" height="266" class="size-full wp-image-371" /> Photo credit goes to <a href="http://twitter.com/viktorhanacek" target="_blank">Viktor Hanacek</a>[/caption]


<p>The website layout is very traditional and you can instantly find the menu. You click around a few pages, have some laughs, click on the red colored links within the content, and somehow get very intrigued in this puppy pop product.</p>

<p>Then you see a line of green text say, "Sold exclusively in certain stores." Well it sure would be nice to know which stores it’s referring to, but you don’t see a link. Except that green text is the link to the information you want. However you don’t realize it because that link is a different color than all the other links on the website and you think they simply wanted that text to stand out.</p>

<p><b>Don’t assume people will know to click on something if it doesn’t look like a link.</b> If you have links on your site then all the links should look like links and be easy to recognize. If that link had been red like the rest of the links on the site you would have clicked it and drove 100 miles to your nearest Pup Pop Mart. (Of course you would. Keep pretending. It’s fun.)</p>

<p>Or that green text should have been underlined to make it more likely people would recognize it as a link. Or better yet, say "Click here to find the store nearest you." Or maybe even better yet, make a green button instead of using green text (I talk about this in the next/final section). Then it's very likely you would have seen the link and found your way to the nearest Pup Pop Mart. Sadly Pup Pop Mart lost your business, and probably a lot of other people’s business because of that one little link not being clear.</p>

<p><b>Non-crazy summary of this section:</b> Don’t assume visitors to your website are clever, even if you know they are. You might catch them on a bad day. Design everything to be easy to understand and be consistent with it. A link is a link is a link. If the links within your content are red, then please don’t make some red and some green unless you use some method other than color to indicate both the green and red words people see are links.</p>


<h2>When to be Inconsistent (But Actually Consistent)</h2>

<p>I keep saying to be consistent, but there actually is a time to be inconsistent. It's when you purposely want something to stand out, like your call-to-action. The thing you most want people to do.</p>

<p><span class="bigbluetext">Imagine:</span> You visit the imaginary website of <b>Okapi Copywriters</b>. (My final example is for the animal lovers who are a little weird. Like me.)</p>

[caption id="attachment_362" align="aligncenter" width="400"]<img src="/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/okapi.jpg" alt="Photo credit goes to Derek Keats." width="400" height="228" class="size-full wp-image-362" /> Photo credit goes to <a href="https://www.flickr.com/photos/dkeats/5269539626" target="_blank">Derek Keats</a>.[/caption]

<p>Like the okapi, who interestingly is closely related to the giraffe and not the zebra, Okapi Copywriters has designed their website using black, white, and brown, while using red for all the links. Except for the big "Hire Us" button on the right side of their site. That button is a nice green color. It’s clearly something to click on because it looks like a button, and the green makes it stand out from the rest of the site.</p>

<p>This is an example of using both consistency and inconsistency deliberately in order to guide a visitor to your website into clicking where you most want them to click, and to avoid them overlooking links.</p>

<h2>A Simple, Useful Strategy</h2>
<p>When in doubt about your design, if you can't watch someone navigate through your website for the first time (I drag in my wife for this) then do your best to imagine you have no prior knowledge of the site and try using it.</p>

<p>Start at the home page and go through the site, noting any difficulties and even the tiniest confusing moments you encounter. Then walk away for a while and return to the site to do it again, but this time beginning your visit on a page other than the home page.</p>

<p>Go through the website again making notes. Address the issues in your notes, choosing clarity and simplicity over originality when in doubt, and your website will be positioned to be dramatically easier for visitors to navigate and take the actions you want them to take.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>350</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-10-16 02:16:58</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-10-16 02:16:58</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>consistent-style</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[How to Stop Confusing Your Users]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_yoast_wpseo_focuskw</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[consistent]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_yoast_wpseo_linkdex</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[92]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_yoast_wpseo_metadesc</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Being consistent with how you style your website can determine whether a visitor becomes a customer or simply leaves confused.]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_encloseme</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_encloseme</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Value Calculator: See the Value You Provide</title>
		<link>http://www.shycyborg.com/value-calculator/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 08:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[david@shycyborg.com]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.shycyborg.com/?p=381</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When it comes time to price a web project, it's incredibly easy to underestimate how much value you'll be providing your client. It's so easy to tell yourself that you won't be doing enough work to warrant charging $10,000 or even $3,000.</p>
<p>I can still fall prey to this, so I put together this tool to visually show me and you just how much money (value) our clients can receive over time thanks to our work. Now this is just an estimate because it only requires limited information about your client's business, but it makes it easy to see if it looks like you'll be providing so much value you should really charge more.</p>
<p><strong>Please enter all values as whole numbers.</strong></p>
<form action="javascript:void(0);" id="valueForm">
<div class="one-half first">
<label for="upfrontCost">Initial Cost of Website<br/><i>(including software fees for first year)</i></label>
<input type="text" name="upfrontCost" value="5000" data-parsley-money />

<label for="monthlyCost">Ongoing Monthly Costs<br/><i>(e.g. hosting fees)</i></label>
<input type="text" name="monthlyCost" value="29" data-parsley-money />

<label for="yearlyCost">Ongoing Yearly Costs<br/><i>(e.g. software renewals)</i></label>
<input type="text" name="yearlyCost" value="450" data-parsley-money/>
</div>
<div class="one-half">
<label for="monthlyRevenue">Client's Monthly Revenue</label>
<input type="text" name="monthlyRevenue" value="8000" data-parsley-money/>

<label for="percentageIncrease">Projected Increase in Revenue<br/><i>(A percentage. Accepts 10 or 10%)</i></label>
<input type="text" name="percentageIncrease" value="15" data-parsley-percentage/>

<label for="numOfMonths">Period of Time to Display</label>
<select name="numOfMonths">
<option value="12">1 year</option>
<option value="24" selected>2 Years</option>
<option value="36">3 Years</option>
<option value="48">4 Years</option>
<option value="60">5 Years</option>
</select>
</div>
<br class="clear"/><br/>
<input type="submit" value="Show Me the Money">
</form>
<br class="clear"/><br/>
<canvas id="valueCanvas" height="450" width="600"></canvas>
<div id="valueTable"></div>
<div id="valueSummary"></div>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>381</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2014-10-29 08:05:20</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2014-10-29 08:05:20</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>value-calculator</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Realize You're Worth More Than You Think]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_encloseme</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_encloseme</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_encloseme</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_encloseme</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>The Computer Doesn&#039;t Make the Developer</title>
		<link>http://www.shycyborg.com/the-computer-doesnt-make-the-developer/</link>
		<pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2015 06:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[david@shycyborg.com]]></dc:creator>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://www.shycyborg.com/?p=410</guid>
		<description></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In 2002 I made my computer science professor angry enough that he "accidentally" poured coffee on my assignment (we handed in printed copies of our code along with floppy disks) and for the rest of the semester he took 20 points off every assignment without explanation.</p>

<p>What was my great sin? I turned in an assignment two weeks early when he insisted it couldn't possibly be completed that quickly. We actually had an amusing argument in the hallway over it.</p>



<blockquote><p>*hand the professor the assignment* "Hi, Professor [What's-Your-Face]. I finished the assignment and wondered if I could turn it in now."</p>

<p>*professor hands the assignment back* "No. You cannot be done."</p>

<p>*hand the assignment back to the professor* "But I am."</p>

<p>*hand back to me* "No. You cannot be finished."</p>

<p>*look at the paper and hand it back* "Yeah...it looks pretty finished."</p></blockquote>



<p>The professor eventually accepted the assignment and walked away in a huff, and I  wandered over to the library to read a few hours, unaware I'd somehow offended the guy with my not-so-social skills.</p>

<p>What allowed me to finish that supposedly weeks-long coding assignment in an hour? Not my computer. In 2002 I was still rocking a bottom-of-the-line Win 98 system. It's because the assignment was fairly basic C++ and I'd been coding in another language in the C family for a few years.</p>

<p>It was my prior experience that allowed me to excel, yet I often hear people talk as though having a Mac or a PC defines whether you're a good developer. I know amazing developers that use Macs, and I know folks that use Windows that could code the pants off a lot of Mac snobs I know.</p>

<p>Having a good tool can make crafting easier, but it is the time put into perfecting the craft that makes you able to use the tools well. I could get the most powerful computer in the world, set it in front of my 3-year-old, and she's not suddenly going to become an elite developer. The same is true for a 23-year-old and a 73-year-old.</p>

<p>Most of the tools I use these days are for the Mac, but that's just because my current computer is a Mac. I still have a Windows PC, and I could still build websites, games, and the majority of stuff on it about as efficiently as I do on my Mac. Some specific tools have nicer implementations on specific systems, but you can almost always find good alternatives.</p>

<p>I currently use a Mac, but could choose to use a PC in the future. My programming skills would not change. The key for you is to first and foremost focus on improving your programming skills, and beyond that find the system on which you are most comfortable, develop a toolset and workflow in which you're comfortable, and put in the time to become efficient with it.</p>

<p>Tools can make your life easier, and some operating systems are easier to use than others, but a programmer is ultimately defined by his or her programming skills. Spend a little time to do some research and get your computer and tools setup so you can program, and then actually do programming. Don't review your setup for 3-6 months. Don't spend more time perfecting your toolset than your ability to use the tools. Otherwise your core skills will never grow and instead of being the best at using tools you'll just sound like one.</p>]]></content:encoded>
		<excerpt:encoded><![CDATA[]]></excerpt:encoded>
		<wp:post_id>410</wp:post_id>
		<wp:post_date>2015-03-20 06:20:19</wp:post_date>
		<wp:post_date_gmt>2015-03-20 06:20:19</wp:post_date_gmt>
		<wp:comment_status>closed</wp:comment_status>
		<wp:ping_status>closed</wp:ping_status>
		<wp:post_name>the-computer-doesnt-make-the-developer</wp:post_name>
		<wp:status>publish</wp:status>
		<wp:post_parent>0</wp:post_parent>
		<wp:menu_order>0</wp:menu_order>
		<wp:post_type>post</wp:post_type>
		<wp:post_password></wp:post_password>
		<wp:is_sticky>0</wp:is_sticky>
		<category domain="category" nicename="uncategorized"><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_edit_last</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_subtitle</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Just Pick Your Tools and Stop Sounding Like a Tool]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_encloseme</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_encloseme</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
		<wp:postmeta>
			<wp:meta_key>_encloseme</wp:meta_key>
			<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[1]]></wp:meta_value>
		</wp:postmeta>
	</item>
</channel>
</rss>
